eturbonews.com 2019-07-11

# eTN Privacy Policy | Buzz travel | eTurboNews |Travel News

eTurboNews, Inc (eTN) publishes this Internet Privacy Policy to inform you of our practices concerning the collection and use of information you provide us through interactions with this website and the other eTN-affiliated websites. This policy is not applicable to information gathered by other methods or controlled by other agreements.

How We Collect Information

eTN collects personal information in a variety of ways, including when you register with eTN on this website, when you subscribe to eTN services through this website, when you use eTN products or services via the website, when you visit eTN websites or the websites of certain eTN partners, and when you enter Internet-based promotions or sweepstakes sponsored or administered by eTN.

User Registration

When you register on our website, we ask for and collect information such as your name, email address, zip code, and industry. For some products and services we may also ask for your address and information about you or your business’s assets or income. Once you register with eTN and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

e-letters

Users may elect to participate in a variety of eTN e-letters (email services), ranging from daily news to supplier hot specials. eTN collects personal information in connection with the registration for and use of such services.

Contests

Users may elect to participate in promotions and/or promotional contests that eTN conducts from time to time on behalf of its clients. eTN collects personal information in connection with user registration for and participation in such promotions and contests.

Educational Programs and Seminars

Users may elect to participate in educational programs and seminars that eTN conducts from time to time. eTN collects personal information in connection with user registration for and participation in such programs.

Cookies

“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. eTN or its advertisers may send a cookie to your computer through your browser. eTN uses cookies to track page requests and the duration of each user’s visit and the use of cookies allows us to provide a user’s browser with information tailored to the visitor’s preferences and needs and to also streamline the user’s visits to our website. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept cookies, your experience at our website and other websites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

IP Addresses

eTN automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, eTN cookie information, and the website page you request. eTN uses this information to help diagnose problems with our servers, for system administration, and to examine our website traffic in aggregate. The information may be collected and used to improve the content of our Web pages and to customize content and/or layout for each user.

Purchases

If you are purchasing something from an eTN website, we need to know personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. This information may also be used by eTN to notify you of related products and services. Credit card information will not be shared or sold to unaffiliated third parties for any purpose without your express permission, except as necessary to process the transaction.

Use of Information

If you elect to provide us personal information, we use it primarily to deliver the service you requested. eTN may use personal information in a variety of ways including the following:

o eTN may use personal information to collected through its website to send out targeted email promotions on behalf of its advertisers and industry partners.

o eTN may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies in order to better deliver products and services that may be of interest and benefit to you.

o eTN may use personal information to contact users regarding renewing subscriptions to eTN services and products.

o eTN may use personally identifiable information to send notification of eTN’s or our partners’ products and services by such methods as email and/or postal mail.

o If you provide financial information, we use that information primarily to verify your credit and collect payments for your purchases, orders, subscriptions, etc.

o eTN may send product announcements or special edition e-letters to online registrants.

o If you participate in an eTN educational program, seminar, or other time-sensitive program, we may contact you to remind you of upcoming deadlines or additional information concerning these programs.

o eTN occasionally conducts subscriber and/or user surveys to better target our content to our audiences. The aggregated information collected is sometimes shared with our advertisers, however, we will do not share specific individual information with a third-party.

o eTN operates several websites featuring its travel-related content and services. eTN may share personal information collected from users of its websites internally across these websites to better serve its users.

eTN has numerous products and services and therefore numerous email and promotion lists. In an effort to allow users to tailor their participation in eTN services and promotions, eTN provides users the ability to choose specific lists or products of interest and opt-out options are product and use/list specific. All email promotions sent from eTN provide an opt-out link at the bottom of the email pursuant to which users can opt-out of specific products and promotions. If you receive one of these emails and wish to unsubscribe please follow the instructions given in each email or contact [subscription@www.eturbonews.com](mailto:subscription@www.eturbonews.com)

From time to time we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our website.

Sharing of Information Collected With Third Parties

In general, eTN does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you have requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

o We may provide personal information about our users to trusted partners and vendors who work on behalf of or with eTN under confidentiality and similar agreements prohibiting such parties’ further use of the information. These companies may use your personal information to help eTN communicate with you about offers from eTN and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to use or share this information.

o When you register for an educational program, contest, or other promotion that is sponsored by a third party, the third party will be provided personally identifiable information unless otherwise posted in connection with the promotion.

o eTN may from time to time share personal information such as email addresses with trusted third parties who deliver content that is likely to be of interest to the user and subject to opt-out obligation on the part of such third party.

o We may share personal information where we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served on eTN, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

o We may share such information where we have a good faith belief that it is necessary in order to investigate (or assist in the investigation of), prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of eTN’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

o If eTN is acquired by or merged with another company, we will transfer information about you to this other company in connection with the acquisition or merger.

Discussion Groups

Email discussion groups are available for our users on some of our websites. Participants should be aware that information disclosed in these discussion lists is made available to all members and thus becomes public information. We suggest that you exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information in such discussion groups.

Security

This website takes commercially reasonable precautions to protect your personal information. When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as credit card and payment information, we re-direct users to industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encrypted servers. As a result, sensitive data you submit to our website such as credit card and payment information is transmitted securely over the Internet.

Disclaimers

eTN is not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. eTN also links to a wide variety of other sites and contains advertisements of third parties. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.

About Children’s Privacy

This eTN website is not intended for use by children and eTN does not knowingly collect information from children. You must be 18 years old to access or use this site.

Update/Change Your Data

To update your email address or change your email preferences please contact  subscription@etn.travel

Changes to this Privacy Policy

eTN reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update or modification on the website. Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon positing on the website. Users will be informed of changes to this Privacy Policy via the “updated as of” link on the eTN website.

What Else Should I Know About My Privacy When Online?

The eTN website contains many hyperlinks to other websites. The eTN website also contains advertisements of third parties. eTN is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party websites or advertisers. eTN does not share any of the individual personal information you provide eTN with the websites to which eTN links, except as stated elsewhere within this Privacy Policy, although eTN may share aggregate data with such websites (such as how many people use our Site).

Please check with those third party sites to determine their privacy policy. When eTN embeds third party content into one of it’s eTN web pages, eTN will use reasonable efforts to advise our users that they have exited an eTN operated website and are entering a third party controlled website. Customers/users should read and understand any privacy policy noted on all third party websites.

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online – for example through email, discussion lists, or elsewhere – that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you’re online.

Your California Privacy Rights

Under a provision of California law, a California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes (“California customer”) is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that if the company has a privacy policy that gives either an opt-out or opt-in choice for use of your personal information by third parties for marketing purposes, the company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options.

Because this Site is intended for use on a business-to-business basis, this provision of California law will not apply, in most cases, to the information collected.

To the extent an California resident using this Site for personal, family, or household purposes seeks information covered the law, this Site qualifies for the alternative option. As stated in our Privacy Policy, users of the Site may opt-out or opt-in to the use of your personal information by third parties. Therefore, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that received your personal information during the preceding year for marketing purposes. To prevent disclosure of your personal information for use in direct marketing by a third party, do not opt-in to such use when you provide personal information on the Site. Please note that whenever you opt-in to receive future communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party’s privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

California residents who utilize this Site for personal, family, or household purposes may request further information about our compliance with this law by e-mailing  publisher@etn.travel You should put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the subject field of your email. Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this email address.

Your Consent To This Policy

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of information by eTN as specified in this policy. Please also note that your use of the website is governed by the eTN Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to the terms of the Privacy Policy or the Terms and Conditions, please do not use the website, products and/or services.

Please send any questions about eTN’s Privacy Policy to publisher@etn.travel

## Additional information

### Plugin: Smush

Note: Smush does not interact with end users on your website. The only input option Smush has is to a newsletter subscription for site admins only. If you would like to notify your users of this in your privacy policy, you can use the information below.

Smush sends images to the WPMU DEV servers to optimize them for web use. This includes the transfer of EXIF data. The EXIF data will either be stripped or returned as it is. It is not stored on the WPMU DEV servers.

Smush uses a third-party email service (Drip) to send informational emails to the site administrator. The administrator’s email address is sent to Drip and a cookie is set by the service. Only administrator information is collected by Drip.
